<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sshd-projects on Apache Mina</title>
    <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sshd-projects on Apache Mina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.1.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.1.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.1.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.1.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.1.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.1.0 Sources (.bz2) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.1.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes While the SSHD server side is maturing, the client side will certainly see some major changes in the future, so that the APIs are not considered stable yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.10.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.10.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.10.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.10.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.10.1 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.10.1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.10.1.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.1 contains 2 minor packaging fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.1 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.1 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.1 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.10.1 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.10.1 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.11.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.11.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.11.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.11.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.11.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.11.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.11.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.11.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.11.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.12.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.12.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.12.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.12.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.12.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.12.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.12.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.12.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.12.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.13.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.13.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.13.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.13.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.14.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.14.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.14.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.14.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.2.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.2.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.2.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.2.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.2.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.2.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.2.0 Sources (.bz2) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.2.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.2.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes. Please report any feedback to users@mina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.3.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.3.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.3.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.3.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.3.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.3.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.3.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.3.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.3.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.4.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.4.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.4.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.4.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.4.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.4.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.4.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.4.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.4.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.5.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.5.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.5.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.5.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes. Please report any feedback to users@mina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.6.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.6.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.6.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.6.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes. Please report any feedback to users@mina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.7.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.7.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.7.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.7.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes. Please report any feedback to users@mina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.8.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.8.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.8.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.8.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes. Please report any feedback to users@mina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 0.9.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.9.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_0.9.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 0.9.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.9.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.9.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 0.9.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 0.9.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA   Individual jars:  Apache Mina SSHD Core 0.9.0 (.jar) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.0.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.0.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.0.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.0.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.1.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.1.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.1.1 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.1.1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.1.1.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.1.1 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.2.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.2.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.2.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.2.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.3.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.3.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.3.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.3.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions N/A</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.4.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.4.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.4.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.4.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions N/A&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.6.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.6.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.6.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.6.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 1.7.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.7.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_1.7.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 1.7.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.0.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.0.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.0.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.0.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.0.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.0.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.0.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.0.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes There have been many bug fixes and improvements since last released version 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.1.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.1.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.1.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.1.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.1.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.1.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.1.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.1.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes A few backward incompatible changes have been made since the previous release, thus the version has been named 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.2.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.2.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.2.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 2.2.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.3.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.3.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.3.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 2.3.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.4.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.4.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.4.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Release Notes Apache Mina SSHD 2.4.0 contains a few enhancements and bug-fixes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.5.0 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.5.0.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.5.0.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.0 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.0 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.0 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.0 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.0 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Please report any feedback to users@mina.apache.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache SSHD 2.5.1 Release</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.5.1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/download_2.5.1.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
Getting the Distributions  Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Please report any feedback to users@mina.apache.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embedding SSHD in 5 minutes</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/embedding_ssh.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/embedding_ssh.html</guid>
      <description>Embedding SSHD in 5 minutes See https://github.com/apache/mina-sshd for more informations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Building</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/building.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/building.html</guid>
      <description>Building SSHD SSHD uses Maven as its build tool. If you don&amp;rsquo;t fancy using Maven you can use your IDE directly or Download a distribution or JAR.
  Download and install Maven.
  Get the latest code from Git
  Build the code with the following command
 mvn clean install    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Contributors</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/contributors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/contributors.html</guid>
      <description>Committers The following is a list of developers with commit privileges that have directly contributed to the project in one way or another.
 Emmanuel L&amp;eacute;charny Guillaume Nodet Lyor Goldstein Shawn Pearce  Contributors The following additional people have contributed to this project through the way of suggestions, patches or documentation.
 Leo Bayer Andr&amp;eacute; Bierwolf Shikhar Bhushan C&amp;eacute;dric Chantepie Patrick Dessalle Ken Diep Laurent Duchesne Richard Evans Francois Fernandes Otto Frost Will Glass-Husain Andreas Johansson Nick Howes Kohsuke Kawaguchi Leonid Kof Bill Kuker Philippe Laflamme Tien Luong Daniel Micol-Ponce David Overton Simon Paradis Bobby Powers Taras Puchko Matthew Schulze Michael Stevens Liu Tao Pete Torgenrud Denis Tulskiy Frank van der Kleij Jason Van Zyl Tim Vernum  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Documentation</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/documentation.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/documentation.html</guid>
      <description>Apache SSHD documentation See https://github.com/apache/mina-sshd for more informations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Downloads</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/downloads.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/downloads.html</guid>
      <description>Latest SSHD Releases The latest release is the SSHD 2.5.1 release. Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 contains a number of enhancements and bug-fixes.
 Source distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Sources (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Sources (.zip) PGP SHA   Binary distributions:  Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Binary (.tar.gz) PGP SHA Apache Mina SSHD 2.5.1 Binary (.zip) PGP SHA    Development snapshots You can build the latest version from sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD FAQ</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/faq.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/faq.html</guid>
      <description>FAQ See https://github.com/apache/mina-sshd for more informations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Features</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/features.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/features.html</guid>
      <description>Features The list of features implemented by Mina SSHD is available at https://github.com/apache/mina-sshd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Getting Involved</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/getting_involved.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/getting_involved.html</guid>
      <description>Getting Involved The Apache SSHD developers communicates using our Mailing Lists. If you have any questions, feedback or suggestions, you&amp;rsquo;re very welcome to join the list and send an email. We are also happy to receive bug reports and feature requests in our JIRA.
Patches The best chance of getting your bug or feature fixed is to provide a patch, if they fit our goals we will usually have them committed within a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Issue Tracking</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/issue_tracking.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/issue_tracking.html</guid>
      <description>Issue Tracking We are using JIRA to track all SSHD issues including bugs. Please visit our issue tracker page to report a bug.
How to report a bug Writing a bug report with detailed information will help us to fix your problem sooner.
 Make sure if the bug you are going to report doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist yet. Attaching JUnit test case which reproduces the problem will put your report in our highest priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/mailing_lists.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/mailing_lists.html</guid>
      <description>Mailing List General information about the SSHD mailing lists can be found here.
For Users Please use this list for any questions regarding how to use SSHD.
         Subscribe users-subscribe@mina.apache.org   Unsubscribe users-unsubscribe@mina.apache.org   Post users@mina.apache.org   Archive http://www.mail-archive.com/users@mina.apache.org/    For Developers We use the MINA developers list for asking technical questions, discussing feature suggestions or general questions regarding the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Overview</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/</guid>
      <description>Overview Apache SSHD is a 100% pure java library to support the SSH protocols on both the client and server side. This library is based on Apache MINA, a scalable and high performance asynchronous IO library.
SSHD does not really aim at being a replacement for the SSH client or SSH server from Unix operating systems, but rather provides support for Java based applications requiring SSH support.
The technical documentation is maintained in the source tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSHD Sources</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/sources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/sshd-project/sources.html</guid>
      <description>Overview Sources for the Apache MINA projects are currently managed through GIT. Instructions on GIT use can be found at http://git-scm.com/book/.
Normal Git Access Anyone can check code out of Git. You only need to specify a username and password in order to update the Git repository, and only MINA committers have the permissions to do that. We run Git over standard HTTPS, so hopefully you won&amp;rsquo;t have problems with intervening firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>