<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asyncweb-projects on Apache Mina</title>
    <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asyncweb-projects on Apache Mina</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AsyncWeb</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/</guid>
      <description>Apache AsyncWeb The **AsyncWeb** project is currently dormant. We don&#39;t have committers for it, so if you feel like you can give an hand, please do contact us !  Apache AsyncWeb (built on top of the Apache MINA network framework) employs non-blocking selector driven IO at the transport level, and is asynchronous throughout - from the initial parsing of requests, right through to and including the services implemented by users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AsyncWeb Contributors</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/contributors.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/contributors.html</guid>
      <description>Contributors Committers The following is a list of developers with commit privileges that have directly contributed to the project in one way or another.
 Jeff Genender Mike Heath Alex Karasulu Emmanuel Lécharny Sangjin Lee Trustin Lee Rick McGuire Julien Vermillard  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AsyncWeb Getting Involved</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/getting_involved.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/getting_involved.html</guid>
      <description>Getting Involved Apache AsyncWeb communicates using our Mailing Lists. If you have any questions, feedback or suggestions, you&amp;rsquo;re very welcome to join the list and send an email. We are also happy to receive bug reports and feature requests in our JIRA.
Patches The best chance of getting your bug or feature fixed is to provide a patch, if they fit our goals we will usually have them committed within a few days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AsyncWeb Reporting Bugs</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/reporting_bug.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/reporting_bug.html</guid>
      <description>Reporting a Bug We are using JIRA to track all AsyncWeb issues including bugs. Please visit our issue tracker page to report a bug.
How to report a bug Writing a bug report with detailed information will help us to fix your problem sooner.
 Make sure if the bug you are going to report doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist yet. Attaching JUnit test case which reproduces the problem will put your report in our highest priority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AsyncWeb Sources</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/sources.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/sources.html</guid>
      <description>Sources for the Apache AsyncWeb projects are currently managed through Subversion (SVN). Instructions on Subversion use can be found at http://svnbook.red-bean.com/. If you are on Windows, the excellent TortoiseSVN client is highly recommended.
For each project you can find a detailed description how to checkout and build the source on the project documentation. This page is just a short overview.
Web Access to Subversion If you just want to browse the source code, you can use the web interface to Subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/documentation.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/documentation.html</guid>
      <description>Documentation AsyncWeb project is currently dormant. The documentation we have can be found on AsyncWeb WIKI</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/references.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mina.apache.org/asyncweb-project/references.html</guid>
      <description>References  Interesting Comet article http://cometdaily.com/2008/04/01/new-technology-new-problems-delayed-pushes-operations/  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>